Finding Aid for the Theodore Bikel Papers LSC.2321
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Correspondence and subject files, 1946-2012
  - Subseries 1.1: Chronological files, 1946-2002
    - H fan, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - I fan, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - I general, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - I personal, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - J general, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - J personal, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Jewish Affairs, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - J fan, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - K fan, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - K general, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - K personal, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Kalahari, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Leventhal, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 6, Box 38, Folder 1)
    - L fan, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - L personal, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - L general, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - M fan, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - M general, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - M personal, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Meetings, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - N general, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - New Zealand, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - N fan, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - N personal, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - NFF, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - O personal, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - O fan, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - O general, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - P fan, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - P general, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - P personal, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Payment transfer, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Poetry, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - R personal, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - R fan, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - R general, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Betty Rosen, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - SAG, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - S fan, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - S general, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - S personal, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - T fan, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - T personal, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - T general, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - VIP, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - V general, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - V fan, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - V personal, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - W fan, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - D. Wittier Co., 1965 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - W personal, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - XYZ general, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - XYZ fan, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - XYZ personal, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - W general, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - A personal, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - A fans, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - A general, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - AEA, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - AJC - Exec. Comm. meetings, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - AJC, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Apartheid, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Artist Agency Corp., 1966 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - ACRAF, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - B general, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - B fans, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - B personal, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Jay Bernstein, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - "Beyond the Mts.", 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - T.B. (Bikel) schedules, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Airlines, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Jos. Bikel correspondence, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - C general, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - C personal, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - C fans, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Carnegie Hall, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - D general, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - D fans, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - D personal, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - E general, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - E personal, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - E fans, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - EBM, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Elektra, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - El Malcriado, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - F general, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - F fans, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - F personal, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - F festival (Philadelphia Folk Festival), 1966 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - G general, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - G personal, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - G fans, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - H general, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - H fans, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - H personal, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Huntington - Hartford, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - I fans, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - I general, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - J personal, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - J fans, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - J general, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Jewish affairs, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - K general, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - K fans, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - K personal, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - (Kalahari), 1966 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - L general, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - L fans, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - L personal, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Leventhal, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Theo - London, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - H. Leventhal master file, 1965-1966 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Yellow slips HL (Leventhal), 1966 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - M fans, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - M general, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - M personal, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - N fans, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - N personal, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - N general, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - NFF (Newport Folk Festival), 1966 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Newport Festival, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - NFF (Newport Folk Festival) minutes, 1963-1967 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - O general, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - O personal, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - O fan, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - P general, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - P personal, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - P fans, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Pousse Cafe, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Q general, 1965-1966 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Royal Festival Hall, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - R general, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - R personal, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - R fans, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - The Russians Are Coming, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - S general, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - S personal, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - S fans, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - SAG, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - 7 Arts work papers & script Karmon-Bavaria, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Soviet anti-Semitism, 1963-1966 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Sov. Jewry vigil, 1965-1966 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Sharon Travel Associates Inc., 1966 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Stray, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - T general, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - U general, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - V general, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - V fans, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - V personal, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - W general, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - W personal, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - W fans, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - White House Conference "To Fulfill These Rights", 1966 (Box 45)
    - XYZ general, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - XYZ fan, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - XYZ personal, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - A general, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - A personal, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - A fan, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - African Queen, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - AFTRA, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Airlines, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - AJC gen. correspondence January - June, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - AJC gen. correspondence June - December, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 3-4)
    - AJC - Governing Coucl. minutes, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - AJC - Exec. Comm. meeting minutes, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - AJC Met. Council minutes, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - AJC - Hillel, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 6, Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Angry Arts, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Artists Agency Corp., 1967 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - B general, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - B personal, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - B fan, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Lane Blackwell - Euravision, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Jos. & Miriam Bikel - correspondence, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence w/ Theo, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Jay Bernstein, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - C general, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - C personal, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - C fan, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - D general, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - D personal, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - D fan, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - (Dissenting Democrats?), 1967 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - EBM - general corresp., 1967 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - EBM - bills sent for payment, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - EBM - oil investments, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - EBM - stock investments general, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - E general, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - E personal, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - E fan, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Elektra, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - F general, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - F personal, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - F fan, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - G general, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - G personal, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - G fan, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - General Artists Corp., 1967 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - H general, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - H personal, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - H fan, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Estate of Lorraine Hansberry, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - I general, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - I personal, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Israel bonds, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - J general, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - J personal, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - J fan, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Jewish State Theatre, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - K personal, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - K general, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - K fan, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Koschland, 1966-1967 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - L general, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - L personal, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - L fan, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Leventhal's deposit slips "yellow slips", 1967 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Commission statements Harold Leventhal, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - H. Leventhal, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - H. L'thal (Leventhal) newsletters, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Luce Press Clipping Service, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - M general, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - M personal, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - M fan, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Mensa, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Magazine subs., 1967 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - "My Side of the Mountain", 1967 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - N fan, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - N personal, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - N general, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - O general, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - O fan, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - P fan, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - P personal, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - P general, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - R personal, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - R general, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - R fan, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - S fan, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - S general, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - S personal, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - "Saint Joan", 1967 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Steve Scheuer, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Screen Actors Guild, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Irving Schlussel, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Sharon Travel, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Sunflower, Mississippi, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Sweet November, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - T general, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - T personal, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - T fan, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - "Noon Wine" Talent Assoc., 1967 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - "Tonight in Person" BBC, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - U general, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - V general, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - V personal, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - V fan, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - W general, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - W personal, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - W fan, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - XYZ general, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - XYZ personal, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - XYZ fan, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - (Notebooks/appointment books), 1964-1967 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - A personal, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - A general, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - American Jewish Congress, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 1-3)
    - AJC - Hillel, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Ben Irving Memorial Fund, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - H general, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - H personal, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - H fan, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Horst Films, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - I general, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - I personal, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - J general, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - K general, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - K personal, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - K fan, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - L general, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - L personal, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - L fan, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Leventhal newsletters, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Luce press clippings, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Leventhal - commission statements, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Leventhal - deposit slips, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Leventhal Mgmt. general, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - M general, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - M personal, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - M fan, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - McCarthy campaign, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Morris Wm., Agency, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Senator Wayne Morse, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - N general, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - N personal, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - N fan, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Newport Folk Festival, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - O general, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - O personal, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - O fan, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - P general, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - P personal, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - P fan, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Q general, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - R general, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - R personal, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - R fan, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - S general, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - S personal, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - S fan, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - T general, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - T personal, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - T fan, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - U general, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - V general, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - V fan, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - W general, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - W personal, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - W fan, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - XYZ general, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - XYZ personal, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - A general, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Alabama Democrats, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - A personal, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - A fan, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - AF of M (American Federation of Musicians), 1969 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - AFL-CIO SPACE (Golodner), 1969 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - AFTRA, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - American Airlines, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - (A loose), 1969 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - AJC general corresp., 1969 (Box 57, Folder 4-6)
    - AJC - BPA Division, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - AJC Campaign Cabinet, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - AJC CJA, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - AJC - CJA activities, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - AJC - youth specialist, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - AJC Exec. Council, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - AJC Gov. Council, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - AJC Rejuvenation Comm. - correspn., 1969 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - AJC Hillel, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - AJC Met. Council, 1969 (Box 58, Folder 6, Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Amnesty International minutes & reports, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Amnesty International correspondence, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - B general, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - B personal, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - B fan, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Bernstein, Jay, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Biafra Committee, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Bikel, Josef & Miriam, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - C general, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - C personal, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - C fan, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Clarke, Buddy, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Concerts - correspondence re, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - D general, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - D personal, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - D fan, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - E general, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - E personal, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - E fan, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - EBM general, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - EBM bills for payment, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - EBM checks for deposit, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - EBM investments, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - EBM oil investments, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Elektra Records, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - F general, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - F personal, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - F fan, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - "Fiddler..." Honolulu/ Herb Rogers, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Fulton, Richard, Inc., 1969 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - G fan, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - G general, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - H general, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - H fan, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - I general, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - J general, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - J fan, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - K general, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - L general, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - L fan, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Leventhal - general, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Leventhal - checks sent to, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Leventhal - commission statements, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Leventhal - deposit slips, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Leventhal - exp. invoices, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Leventhal - newsletters, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Luce press clippings, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - (Lindsay campaign NYC), 1969 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - M general, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - M personal, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - M fan, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Morris Agency - general, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Morris Agency - commission statements, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - N general, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - N personal, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - NDC, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Newport Folk Festival, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - O general, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - O personal, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - O fan, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Orders received, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - P general, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - P fan, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - P personal, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - People's Theatre, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Q general, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - R general, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - R personal, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - R fan, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - S general, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - S fan, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - S personal, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Schneider, Richard, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Screen Actors Guild, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Schlussel, Irwin E., 1969 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Sharon Travel Assoc., 1969 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - T general, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - T personal, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - T fan, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - U general, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - V general, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - V personal, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - V fan, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - W general, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - W personal, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - W fan, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - 3 WSV/ Wm. White/ Aurelio, 1967-1969 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - (WITF-TV), 1969 (Box 64, Folder 5-6)
    - XYZ general, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - XYZ personal, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - XYZ fan, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - ("Youth" file?), 1968-1969 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1960s (Box 65, Folder 3)
      Includes original and copies of correspondence with government officials, first ladies, and others regarding 1960s protests and civil rights.
    - AJC 1966 Convention (accordion file) (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - 1968 National Democratic Convention (accordion file) (Box 66, Folder 2-6)
    - Clippings - not for book (accordion file), 1960s (Box 66, Folder 7, Box 67, Folder 1-2)
    - Newport Folk Festival (accordion file), 1963-1968 (Box 67, Folder 3-6)
    - Newport Folk Fest - press & programs (accordion file), 1960-1969 (Box 68, Folder 1-3)
    - Scheuer-for-Mayor campaign material (accordion file), 1968-1969 (Box 224, Folder 5-6)
    - A general, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - A personal, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - AF of M, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - AFL-CIO (SPACE) Golodner, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - AFTRA, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - AJC Stephen Wise awards dinner, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - AJC general, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 3-4)
    - AJC Hillel, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - AJC Youth Committee, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - AJC Nat'l. Convention, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - AJC Exec. Committee corresp., 1970 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - AJC Comm. on Int'l Affairs, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - AJC - CJA div. activities, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - AJC CJA, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - AJC Gov. Council minutes, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - AJC Rejuv. Committee, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 6, Box 71, Folder 1)
    - AJC Rejuvenation Comm., 1968-1970 (Box 71, Folder 2-3)
    - (AJC Rejuvenation Committee), undated (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Alfa Auto Rental, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Amer.-Israel Cultural Fdn - Arts Council, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Amnesty International minutes, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Amnesty International corresp., 1970 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - B general, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - B personal, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Close of Bank of North America, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Jay Bernetein Publ. Rel., 1970 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Bikel, Josef & Miriam, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - C general, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - C personal, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - C fan, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Cinema Center Films - "Darker Than Amber", 1970 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - D general, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - D personal, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - D fan, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Decter, Moshe, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Duffey, Rev. Joseph 1970 primary campaign in Conn. (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - E general, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - E personal, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - EMB investments, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - EBM oil investments, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Elektra Records, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Encounter Films Inc., 1970 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Encounter Films: projects submitted for consideration, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - F general, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - F personal, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Fan A - Z, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Foster Parents Plan Inc., 1970 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - R. Fulton, Inc., 1970 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - G general, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - G personal, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - H personal, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - I personal, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - I general, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - J general, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - J personal, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Jewish Television Council, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Jewish Theological Seminary, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - K general, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - K personal, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Kaminska Friends of Ida Daminska Theatre, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - L general, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - L personal, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Leventhal - deposit slips, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Leventhal - comm. stmnts, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Luce press clippings, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - M general, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - M personal, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - N general, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - N personal, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Nat'l. Committee for the Recording Arts, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Nat'l. Jewish Music Cncl., 1970 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - National Jewish Welfare Board, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Newport Folk Festival, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - O general, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - O personal, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Orders received, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Orders, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 3)